

CONTACT

+358 0449239180

✓ tsranathunga@gmail.com

(in) https://www.linkedin.com/in/tharaka-ranathunga-58ba52205/

https://github.com/TharakaRanathunga

Kivikatu 5 B 51, 15700, Lahti

SKILLS

Team Player

Public Relations

Time Management

Leadership

Effective Communication

Critical Thinking

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Sinhala (Mother tongue)

English (Fluent)

Chinese (Good)

Japanese (Good)

Finnish (Basic)

TKT CLILL - Band 4

PTE - 78

HSK Level 4

JLPT Level 3

CERTIFICATES

Hygiene Passport

THARAKA RANATHUNGA

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated professional with a proven track, a strong team player who thrives on collaboration, and a committed learner who takes up challenges. I am also a hard worker who always tries to complete the responsibilities taking the optimum output in providing the academia with the best production with knowledge, expertise and research.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ADVERTISEMENT DISTRIBUTOR (PART-TIME) SSM OY

28/08/2024 - Present Lahti

• Sorting and delivering advertisements

LECTURER - SABARAGAMUWA UNIVERSITY OF SRI LANKA

03/05/2020 - 30/06/2024 Belihuloya, Sri Lanka

- Teaching Mandarin Chinese and Japanese to undergraduates Curriculum
- designing Assessing and evaluating students' works Organizing and
- conducting workshops, field tours, seminars, conferences and examinations
- Taking minutes of meetings, recording and reporting

INSTRUCTOR - SRI LANKA INTERNATIONAL BUDDHIST ACADEMY

15/01/2018 - 30/04/2020 Colombo, Sri Lanka

- Designing course content
- Teaching Chinese and English language to undergraduates and diploma students Assessing and evaluating students' works
- Conducting meetings, workshops and events

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN INDUSTRIAL INFORMATION
TECHNOLOGY-LAB UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES, LAHTI, FINLAND
15/08/2024 - PRESENT

CONTENT AND LANGUAGE INTEGRATED LEARNING - AUSTRALIAN COLLEGE OF BUSINESS AND TECHNOLOGY

MASTER OF ARTS IN LINGUISTICS - UNIVERSITY OF KELANIYA, SRI LANKA 19/04/2019-01/05/2023

BACHELOR OF ARTS - SABARAGAMUWA UNIVERSITY OF SRI LANKA 16/07/2013 - 10/11/2017

CERTIFICATE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF BUSINESS MNAGEMENT, SRI LANKA

RESEARCH AND PUBLICATION

- · Acquisition of Chinese Phonetics by University Students
- · Acquisition of Chinese Aspirated Sounds by Beginner Chinese Learners
- A Study on Tourism Oriented Elementary Oral Chinese Theory and Practical Textbooks Compilation
- A Study on the Impact of Task-Based Language Teaching on Improving Chinese Writing Skills
- A Study on the Challenges Faced in Online Chinese Language Learning in Sri Lanka During the Covid-19 Pandemic